<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Guide on</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/</link><description>Recent content in User Guide on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Administrator/Categories</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/categories/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/categories/</guid><description>This section deals with managing category groups in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Categories gives access to the list of category groups.
A Category groups is made of a tree structure of sub category groups and categories. These elements can be re-organized in whatever order the user sees fit.
Category groups can be reused across multiple forms allowing you to generate statistics and reports across multiple types of form to compare.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Department</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/department/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/department/</guid><description>This section deals with managing departments in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Department gives access to the list of departments.
Departments List # Department list overview The list of child departments for the currently selected department. In this view we can filter departments by if they are Active, Inactive or All.
You can create a new department that will become a child department of the currently selected department.
Furthermore one can add permissions/roles to the department limiting the access to the department to users with either user types containing the permissions/roles or roles added directly on the user.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Document Administrator</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_manager/</guid><description>This section deals with managing documents in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Document Administrator gives access to the document manager.
Document Manager # document_manager_1.png The document manager is the heart of the document management system. It allows for organizing documents, creating new ones, upload existing ones, edit or deactivee existing ones.
document_manager_3.png As we can see from the filter we can slice and dice the documents visible in the document manager to zero in on a specific document.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Form Types</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/form_types/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/form_types/</guid><description>This section deals with managing form types in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Form Types gives access to the list of form types.
Form Types serve as a grouping of forms allowing us to set some settings that will be shared by all the forms based on a specific form type.
Risk models List # One can filter form types by their status as Active or Inactive or see All of them.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Forms</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/forms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/forms/</guid><description>This section deals with managing forms in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Forms gives access to the list of forms.
Forms Listing # List of all current forms Shows the list of forms registered in the system. You can filter by Active, Inactive and All forms as well as search by text. For more filtering options. you can click the apply filter button to bring up the sidebar.
Filter form list We have the following filters available for the forms listing.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Preferences</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/preferences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/preferences/</guid><description>This section deals with managing preferences in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Preferences gives access to the list of preferences.
General Settings # The General settings lets you control the following properties.
Property Description Login title The title shown when the user is going to enter their username and password. Email sending for tenant Enable/Disable email sending for all tenant users. Case related # These preferences control basic due data and notification settings.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Questionnaires</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/questionnaires/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/questionnaires/</guid><description>This section deals with managing questionnaires in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Questionnaires gives access to the list of questionnaires.
Questionnaires List # Questionnaires are used to create long questionnairs and check lists that can span either a single page or multiple pages.
You can filter between Active, Deactive or All status, search by title and if the questionnaire is published or not.
Create Questionnaire # General Tab # Creating a questionnaire requires the following field.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Riskmodels</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/risk_models/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/risk_models/</guid><description>This section deals with managing risk models in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Riskmodels gives access to the list of risk models.
Risk models List # The list of risk models can be filtered by active/deactive or all. You can also activate / deactive risk models making them not visible when creating new category groups. Finally clicking the Create button will allows us to create a new Risk model.
Create new Risk Model # General Pages # To create a new Risk Model we need to specify a name for the risk model (it supports multiple languages).</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Rules</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/rules/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/rules/</guid><description>This section deals with managing rules in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Rule gives access to the list of rules.
Rules Listing # There are two main rules categories.
Type Description Workflow rules Rules related to case handling. Notification rules Rules related to sending notifications due to case handling. Create Workflow Rules # A Workflow rule is a rule that is taking into account during processing of a case. The rule categories available are.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Tokens</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/tokens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/tokens/</guid><description>This section deals with managing tokens in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Tokens gives access to the list of tokens.
Tokens Listing # API Tokens Listing Mobile users logged in Listing There are two main types of tokens in the system.
Token Type Description API Tokens Tokens used to integrate with Q using external applications or code. Mobile users logged in An overview of Mobile Application tokens, allowing us to view who uses the Mobile App and also revoke access.</description></item></channel></rss>