<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Guide on</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/</link><description>Recent content in User Guide on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dashboards</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/dashboards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/dashboards/</guid><description>This section deals with managing dashboards for the user.
Clicking on the Dashboards gives access to the list of the users dashboards.
Overview # Dashboards are collections of components that you can build to monitor the state of the platform. You can build dashboards for specific objectives or to make specific information available. There are two types of dashboards.
Type Description User Dashboards the user themselves can build, with components available for them.</description></item><item><title>Cases board</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/case_board/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/case_board/</guid><description>This section deals with using the Cases board.
Clicking on the Cases board gives access to Cases board.
Handling the Case board # case_board_1.png The case board is the easiest and powerful way of managing cases for workflows. It lets you move cases between states easily, filter the board by different criteria and access the case information.
Option Description Select the workflow Select between the workflows you have access to, allowing you to switch between case boards.</description></item><item><title>Documents</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/documents/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/documents/</guid><description>This section lets you browse the published document dashboards, access the documents and favorite documents.
Clicking on the Documents gives access to the document dashboards published.
Document dashboards # documents_1.png The Documents menu gives the user access to all the document dashboards visible for the user given their department and permissions.
documents_2.png The user can navigate between list by clicking on the arrow next to the current dashboard name, as well as click on documents to open a document.</description></item><item><title>Reports</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/reports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/reports/</guid><description>This section deals with creating and updating reports.
Clicking on the reports gives access to the list of the reports available.
Reports lets you build reports of data in Q than can be used to monitor and report on statistics of the data collected.
There are two categories of reports in the system.
Type Description Normal Reports Normal reports made up of graphs and predefined canned graphs. Risk Reports Risk reports made up risk report elements.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Department</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/department/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/department/</guid><description>This section deals with managing departments in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Department gives access to the list of departments.
Departments List # Department list overview The list of child departments for the currently selected department. In this view we can filter departments by if they are Active, Inactive or All.
You can create a new department that will become a child department of the currently selected department.
Furthermore one can add permissions/roles to the department limiting the access to the department to users with either user types containing the permissions/roles or roles added directly on the user.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/User</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/user/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/user/</guid><description>This section deals with managing users in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/User gives access to the list of users.
User List # User list overview The user list shows you all the available users in the system. In this view we can choose between seeing the Active, Inactive and All users.
The search field lets you do a free text search to filter the users you currently see by first, middle or lastname as well as email and phone number.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/User Types</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/usertypes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/usertypes/</guid><description>A user type is a collection of roles. It is used to create specific grouping of permissions and give them a name. Examples of user types can be Administrator, Employee, Inspector where each usertypes contains a set of roles that gives the user permissions to perform different actions or have access to specific features of the platform.
Main Administrator Screen # New workflow dialog Clicking on the Administrator/User Types gives access to the list of user types.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/User Permissions</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/roles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/roles/</guid><description>This section deals with managing user permissions in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/User Permissions gives access to the list of all available permissions.
There are two types of permissions in the system.
Type Description System System permissions are permissions that control the access to sections or actions in the application itself and provided from the application. These might be permissions that let you administer users for example or view reports.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Document Administrator</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_manager/</guid><description>This section deals with managing documents in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Document Administrator gives access to the document manager.
Document Manager # document_manager_1.png The document manager is the heart of the document management system. It allows for organizing documents, creating new ones, upload existing ones, edit or deactivee existing ones.
document_manager_3.png As we can see from the filter we can slice and dice the documents visible in the document manager to zero in on a specific document.</description></item><item><title>Administrator/Document Dashboards</title><link>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_dashboard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.qmplus.app/docs/userguide/document_dashboard/</guid><description>This section deals with managing documents in the system.
Clicking on the Administrator/Document Dashboards gives access to the document manager.
Document dashboards are how you organize the publishing of documents for end users to see. They let you pick from your document library (as represented by the document manager) and build structure components or search components to show the documents to users.
List of Document Dashboards # document_dashboards_1.png The list of dashbaords show you basic information about the dashboards, including title, creation date, department the dashboard is registered on, the visibility and position in the list of dashboards the user will see.</description></item></channel></rss>